[Music]
hey hey welcome back you made it to the
final day so today we're going to do
something a little bit different we're
gonna deal with code blocks
so no more text-based programming as
always I'm here with my my faithful
keeper McKinley McKinley are you ready
for the final day yeah are you excited
to learn about code blocks instead of
text based programming yes she's had
about enough of that expertise
programming it's good for you to learn I
exposed to to you some I've been now
we're kind of going back to more block
these things so here's what we're
building today so this is block based
coding kind of like scratch or tinker or
something like that so you're gonna drag
over code from like a tool box so it's
somewhere in that regard but the thing
that you're doing with that code is
you're building 3d models with it so the
thing that we're gonna do first is we're
gonna build the rocket so that's the
same thing that we built with the 3d
modeler on the first day but now we're
going to build it in a totally different
way you can also do like silly little
animations and things with it if you
would like right that's gonna be the
first example we do together and then
the next one's gonna be a more complex
example we're gonna build a trophy which
would be kind of interesting so you can
see it makes kind of a little animation
of all the steps we're gonna do here
it's actually a pretty complex design
but we're gonna do it together
but I thought I'd show you kind of one
easy on one complex design another thing
I'll say about 3d parts which is fun is
if you have access to a 3d printer or
you would like to order it online you
can actually print your 3d parts so I
have access to a 3d printer I will tell
them and so I printed this right so it's
a trophy it actually says Dave Fischer
on here I doubt you can see the letters
very well but it's fun to be able to
print things just to kind of know that
you can do that what I actually had to
do to print it is I actually had to
export this one as a perk file and then
I opened it up in the 3d modeler and
then from here it's pretty easy to
export an STL file that's if you're
printing it yourself
or you can click on 3d print and you can
actually like send it to one
companies like print the thing or
something like that and they will print
it for you and then mail it to you
obviously you have to pay for that
service but doesn't know that that's
something you could do if you wanted
alright so let's go and get started so
go to Tinkercad dashboard and go down to
code blocks my guess is that you don't
have any code blocks and yours I've got
a few in mind I said go ahead and click
on create new code block and like all
Tinkercad tools the first thing that's
going to happen is it's going to open up
your new project which would be blank
and it's got the new design as well here
and it's gonna give it some crazy name
right so we're used to the the crazy
name game
and so let's go ahead and fix the crazy
name to start things off I don't even
understand the name that I got today so
this is my rocket and if I wanted to I
could put in like a five rocket so
here's how code blocks works just like
scratch or tinker there's commands over
on the right there's different
categories for commands you can see
their shapes
there's modify there's control there's
math there's data there's markup and
then there's the area for your code kind
of like your your workspace and then
there's the stage over here this is like
you know your actors your performing
their their job so let's go ahead and
start off with a cylinder so go ahead
and drag a cylinder from the command
comet and drop it into your code and go
ahead and hit play just to see what
happens so what happens is this your
code says add cylinder the cylinder is
orange but if you change your code let's
say we wanted it to be a silver cylinder
I could change my code now it's a silver
cylinder you could also expand this out
and you could change the properties of
it so let's say I wanted a height of 40
for my rocket and if I change the height
to be 40 you can see that the cylinder
is about taller you can play with
different numbers if you wanted play
around to your heart's content with
changing the radius and the height and
things like that number of sides won't
really be a big impact you can see that
the cylinder is an approximation so it's
got 20 sides on it so it's not really a
perfect circle that's just how
Pro Grip work being play with radius in
high security code now you'll notice
that what it did is it put this cylinder
right at the middle so it's middle is at
zero zero zero so this red line right
here this is the x-axis this green line
right here this is the y-axis and this
blue line right here this is the z-axis
and put the middle of the park right at
zero zero zero so what I want to do for
my rocket is I want to move it up that's
a command that's in modified so it kind
of makes sense that shapes is where you
add new things and then modify is how
you you know modify them since it put
this thing right in the middle and it's
40 tall I want to move it up 20 in the Z
direction so if I run it now you can see
that it makes my cylinder and then it
moves it up 20 cool so let's go ahead
and do some more stuff by the way the
zoom features over here is the same as
it was from the first day you can hold
down the right mouse button to kind of
rotate around if you have a mouse you
can hold down the scroll wheel to kind
of pan around and you can also zoom in
and out with this protocol I do
recommend a mouse for this because it's
not 3d modeling but it's close
alright that's going to add the code
next so will kind of get used to this
pattern but if we want to add an object
that's a command that's up in shapes so
I'm going to add a code there's no harm
in just running it see what it does you
can see they put the code on down there
all right I want a different color code
you can pick any color you'd like I
think I'm gonna go with red ah the
height and the radius of the cone I'm
actually okay with so I think I'm just
gonna leave those alone but I do want it
to be red and then I do want to modify
it to where I move it up some so it's 20
tall so it must be at negative 10 like
the bottom of it's gotta be down at
negative 10 so I want to move it up
there is sometimes a little bug with
that
oh and that so what did I do wrong can I
move it
and what should I have done yeah I
should have moved it up all the way to
the top of the cylinder ten wasn't
enough I actually want to do 10 plus the
height of the cylinder so 10 plus 40 I
won't even bother asking Emily she knows
she can do that 50 cool and there I have
a little cone on top alright let's add
the fins so we're cruising along in the
easy way
so the fins are a star is what we put on
just like 3d modeling there's two
different stars there's this yellow star
which has to be five sided can't be
anything but five sided and it has to
kind of look like the picture there the
one we want is this blue star because
it's got all kinds of like bells and
whistles and features and things you can
change one thing you can change about is
of course the color
I feel like make a nice orange fins pick
any color you'd like but one nice thing
about this one is it defaults to five
sides so you kind of see that's what it
looks like with five sides but I choose
to have my rocket with four sides so I'm
gonna make a four-sided object
now there's other things that I like to
fix it looks like my fins are kind of
too fast
right so they're they're just a little
too fat in the middle that's the inner
radius percentage instead of point zero
five or sorry incident with zero point
five
I'm going to use something smaller
there's no magic answer here I'm going
to use 0.15 so that'll kind of look more
like things so that's good I also
learned to be quite a bit taller right
now their height this 10 I'm gonna make
their height to be 40 so I run it and so
now their height this 40 cool and so
it's going pretty good
what I need to do next is I need to move
it up into position and I think this is
the one that has the weird little blog
as far as the height I'll just try it
and see what see what happens so to move
this up into position what I want to do
is its height this 40 so it should be a
movement up of 20 I'm not sure if that
works so I try it here yeah and then a
weird little bug
move you're too tall I I don't know what
to say about that maybe it'll be fixed
by the time you get to it and that would
be great but it moved it five too much
so I only want to move it 15 sometimes
in programming I can make sense of why
things happen sometimes I just change it
to do what I want right but there is a
pretty cool little rocket so we did that
quickly but the nice thing about block
based coding is you can just see my code
right so it's just sitting right here
and so you can keep messing with yours
until you make it look like mine so
that's kind of the end of the rocket but
we're gonna do a couple extra things
with it just to kind of show you some
ways so here's what we're gonna do first
all these parts are really kind of part
of a group right and so you'll notice
that whenever I say move it just applies
to the last shape but if I wanted to do
something that applied to all of the
shapes I could make them into a group so
here's what I'm gonna do I'm gonna click
on create group and I'm gonna put it on
here normally create group like in
regular 3d modeling would make them all
the same color but the default in blocks
is to make them multicolored so that
makes them a group now that doesn't
appear to have done anything at all but
it did and here's what it did now if I
do modify commands it's going to apply
to the whole group together so just for
fun what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna do a
loop that repeats four times and my goal
is to make this rocket kind of appear to
blast off right so it'll be kind of neat
and so here's what I want to do I want
to rotate and since I created a group
it's going to rotate my whole rocket I'm
gonna rotate about the x axis
which is right here and I'm gonna do
four rotations that are all 180 degrees
so that should basically be two flips so
we're not done yet but go ahead and run
it and see what happens
it builds my rocket and then it spins at
180 spin to 180 spin to 180 spin to 180
it's kind of interesting also I'll
mention that you'll notice that mine
runs at a certain speed that is based on
my computer
yours might run slower if yours runs
slower I recommend you you crank up the
speed to try and get it as fast as you
can you see if I crank up the speed it
goes too fast
the some computers do run faster slower
all right so it's almost done it doesn't
look like it's blasting off right now
though it just looks like it's like
spinning in place in order to make it
look like it's blasting off what I want
to do is instead of rotating about the
middle right here I want to rotate about
some point down here and then that way
it'll kind of look like it's kind of
blasting off and kind of like an art you
gotta go out of you and then it'll come
back again so I can blast off the second
time so what we want to do is we want to
change the pivot point of this rotate
about command and I want to make the
pivot point be somewhere like down here
so somewhere down here is this green
line that's the y-direction
so this is down like negative like I
don't know negative 150 in the Y that's
where I want to rotate around so I want
to drop something into this little
circle that says from pivot that's going
to be in math and here you can find
there's an X Y Z command and math and I
want to rotate around on negative 1 5 0
and so now if I run it it's gonna build
my rocket and so then it's gonna blast
it off and it's going to kind of loop
around and so depending on your on your
Vantage it'll look like a good blast off
or not I'll another thing I should
mention McKinley just had this book she
had her speed all the way up
I want your speed all the way up you
won't see an animation regardless of
your computer speed so make sure you put
it to the middle so that you can see the
animation even if your computer slow it
all will play the animation that way
another thing you can do which is fun
this again depends on your computer
speed you can click on share so I
clicked on share there and it kind of
fast but you can export this as an
animated gif file I don't know what you
know about gif files but their files
that are actually multiple images in
them and you can download an animated
gif file it takes a little bit to finish
but once you've got that file you can
like email that to other people and it
should kind of show the animation
Jaffar away from mine to finish here
alright so mine finished creating the
the jet file and I downloaded here now
what you can do if you wanted is you
could like email this jet file to
someone and be kind of fun so I took
that jet file I dropped it into this
email message and what a gift file will
do so I just said it to McKenna here
what a jiff file should do as it should
kind of play an animation to somebody
the team of it to you which is kind of
neat great alright back back to the the
goal the exporting can be fun you can
also export it as a part and then you
can open it over in the 3d model or
which is fun that's how you get things
printed as well alright so it's going to
open up a new project so that was the
easy one
I never comes the hard one right so I
thought we'd just do one hard one
together I thought it'd be fun to do a
trophy your last day of coding camp so
this is it you're making your own trophy
right so we don't give you a trophy are
you just gonna make your own either
couldn't say new design get yourself set
up with the new design as always there's
a crazy name up here so this is my final
trophy and so when I'm done with this
trophy is I've kind of figured out all
the dimensions in advance so I've kind
of got my notes here so we're gonna
cheat and we're gonna use some of my
dimensions that I kind of figured out in
advance but the way you develop these
things is little by little right so you
kind of you try a number you see how
that look so you just get down on paper
what you think it's gonna be I'm gonna
try it and it's this inner process of
like getting better and better and
better but we're gonna kind of jump to
the final answer just to kind of keep it
keep the video moving so let's go and
get started so what I want to do first
is I want to make this top cup so it's
like a cup that sits on top here the
part that's going to help me the most
with that is a paraboloid so I'm gonna
start by bringing over paraboloid this
paraboloid I choose to make it kind of a
gold color you can make it any color you
like and I want it to have a radius of
40 and a height also of 40
now if you run it right now it'll make
you're probably so you can look at it
it's kind of pretty on there it's upside
down and it's too low so I need to
rotate it so let's go ahead and click on
the rotate here I'm going to choose to
rotate it about the x-axis that's this
red line and I'm going to rotate it 180
degrees so now it's facing the correct
direction the next thing it is is it's
too low for me so I'm going to move it
up I know this is kind of a weird number
but I'm going to move it up 65 so what
that did is by being up 65 it made the
top of this thing via 85 so the height
is 40 half of 40 is 20 20 plus 65 is 85
so that's where it's at right there so
that's going good it's kind of a little
higher the next problem is it's not
actually a cup right it's just like a
solid thing so what I want to do is I
want to cut out the middle to make it a
cup well the way you can do that is to
add another paraboloid
except for instead of like setting a
solid color click on this button right
here which says to make it a hole so
this is going to make a cutout which
would be kind of neat now I want it to
be a little smaller than the original
paraboloid I'm going to make its radius
35 and its height 30 I know it seems
like I made that one 5 less than that
one 10 less but really the the diameter
is 80 over here for the diameter here is
70 so it's 10 less in diameter and then
the height goes from 40 to 30 now it
also is going to be upside-down I could
run it but I know that that's gonna be a
problem so I'm gonna have to flip it
over what the heck I will run it here
just so you can see it and then it's
also at the same also at the wrong
height so we need to move it up so that
it's top is also up here at 85 now to
get it to 85 it has a height of 30 so
we're going to need to bring it up 55
that right now it has a height of 30
which half of that
fifteen so to get it to 85 we have to
move it up to 70 and again the first
time I did this I didn't get it right
the first time I messed it up Buddha law
many times but you can play with these
numbers that's the fun thing about code
blocks you play with them and you see
what it does and you play with them and
you see what it does cool all right next
up I want to actually cut out this whole
in order to actually cut out that whole
it's the same as we did with 3d modeling
you create them as a group so I'm gonna
go ahead and round here and then as soon
as I say create group that actually kind
of like cuts out my hole so now I have a
cup which is pretty cool I next thing I
want to do is I want to have a stem
that's kind of below the cop so this is
gonna be my cylinder for the stem here
so let's go and see if we can make a
cylinder stem so I find a cylinder and I
choose to make it a gold color as well
again you can make it any color you'd
like I my stem that I'm gonna make I'm
gonna have a height of 40 that's kind of
want to use for my rock and I kind of
like forty twelve days now I'm gonna
need to move it up to position as well
and the thing that makes it kind of come
to the bottom look good is a move of
three I run that and so that'll kind of
like connect it to the bomb and again it
was just a guess in check until I
figured out that thirty was a good
height now it's off the ground some
amount it had a height of forty so that
half of that is twenty and then we moved
it up thirty so it's actually up above
the ground by ten right now so the next
thing that I put if I want to run it up
to the bottom of that I need to get it
to ten all right so I want to make this
block right here but up to the bottom of
that in my brain this is like a wooden
block so I'm going to make it kind of a
wooden color so what I'm going to do is
I'm going to add a rectangle box this
box I'm going to make kind of a wooden
color so kind of pick a brown again you
can pick a brown or you pick what
everyone and this thing I'm gonna make
line 30 in late and 10 in the height so
it's going to be 10 tall so it's going
to fill that gap perfectly now if it's
Tim tall I do have to move it up five
just so that it kind of comes up to
ground level by the way I wish that they
had just made when you put a block on
that it's bottom ones at zero but they
did it different maybe they'll change
the rhyme someday but you can see that
there I've got like a little block so
now I have the top part of my trophy and
it's going pretty good
now this trophy is not the finished
product so I want to take this whole
thing and move it up now as you can see
here is if I put on a move command now
it's just going to move the last shape
right that's how it works
okay each of these shapes is kind of
like a divider so what I'm going to do
if I want to move the whole thing up 100
I've got to make it a group so I'm gonna
create a group now and now that
basically says hey everything above me
is a group and I'm going to move the
whole darn thing up 100 and this is just
an amount so that it'll make room for
the rest of my trophy which is coming
below so there the whole thing moves up
cool so now I've got room for the middle
of my trophy the bottom wooden plaque
and then my name that's been as well now
I think this is like a pretty like
isolated chunk whenever you work in
bigger projects it's kind of nice to
keep your isolated chunks like separate
so here's what I'm gonna do I'm gonna
grab this create new object I kind of
grew up with two of them there on
accident just a second I'm gonna say
create new objects and I'm gonna give it
a name we're going to call it top now
what does that really do it does a
couple things it makes this whole object
to be called top which is kind of nice
and if I ever wanted to duplicate it I
could do something like that sometimes
with code blocks you can duplicate
things easily but really what I wanted
to do is I just want to make this like a
single chunk of code so that I can start
working on something
now and I won't get messed up by the
food that was in here so this next
section I'm going to start with a create
new object and I'm just going to call
this one middle and these blocks kind of
help keep things isolated as well right
so now I don't have to worry about
interference between the top section I'm
in the middle section so for the middle
section what I want to do is I want two
cylinders and a bottom rectangle that's
going to be kind of like my middle
section so let's go ahead and do a
cylinder and just like before I kind of
like think of these as gold this
cylinder is gonna have a height of 80
and then I'm going to move it up into
position but I'm also going to move it
over so the value that I'm gonna move
this one is negative 30 30 negative 30
and the axe that moves it over to the
side and then six bolts all go and watch
my animation Banyon notice that I do
have to kind of wait for my whole
animation to finish if you ever get sick
of like watching your animation
feel free to crank the speed all the way
up and then depending on your computer
it'll build it out of faster speed with
no animation effect
alright see if you can pause the video
and look at the pattern we use for this
cylinder and make the cylinder for the
other side alright let's go ahead and do
the wooden block that's on the bottom so
we need a box and I think of it as wood
and this one is 120 wide 30 because of
link but I think that's kind of like the
depth and then the height on this one we
are going to use it 40 and then I'll
have to move that into position as well
since it's 20 tall I'm going to move it
up okay by the way if you get sick of
like the time needed to do things what
you can do is you can actually change
the order of your code if you want
so for example
I'm gonna show it a demo here for
example if this code is before that one
it'll show that one first right and so
if yours is running slow and it's kind
of annoying you can always do the thing
you care about most first and then put
the other stuff later and then you can
just pause it if you don't want to see
the later stuff right mine is still
running sufficiently fast so I don't
have a need to worry about it it's a
reset it here
and so if I want to I can just crank up
my superior it just gets done great so
that's the middle section now that
middle section is done I always kind of
liked it this is just personal
preference I always kind of like to end
these create new objects with a create
group at the bottom I just kind of like
to do it that way so now that section is
alright so the only thing we have left
is the tricky bit so this front namely
so I want to say your name and then I
want it to have kind of like a like a
gold plaque like pleat to it I saw what
we're gonna do is we're gonna add some
text and then we're gonna also have like
a gold plate to it now for this one I
will go ahead and put it at the very top
of my code just so that happens first
and I'm gonna give it a name
so this is my named Li you can spell the
name however you wanted I kind of did it
in a weird style there that's high name
my variable is what I could so I kind of
did it that way
name it whatever you want and the nice
thing about it being at the top is that
as I add things so first I'm gonna add
some text
and my text is gonna say D for sure but
since this is the very first thing in my
program what I can do is I can actually
just use this step by step button and
every time I click this step by step bar
um it does just one line of code so
that's another way that you can develop
big projects with code blocks right so
it did just that one step and then
whenever I want to run it again I just
reset it and I just step through kind of
one by one so what I want to do first is
I want my lettering to be black so I'm
gonna reset it and run through just two
steps
now you'll notice that there's not many
options on text there's how high do you
want it so that's the height here that's
the only thing you can really adjust I'm
gonna make mine be a height of 2 so that
way it's relatively flat it's not
completely flat like ink would be so
that if you do 3d print it you could
actually see like some bump now I also
want to shrink it down a little bit
my name is such that the amount I need
to shrink mine
is 0.65 I've done this before and I know
that 0.65 and the X 0.65 in the Y and
then there's no need to shrink the
z-direction that's the height so that
it's fine I happen to know that that
fits pretty well now if your name is
longer because it didn't mean to hit if
your name is longer you might need to
shrink it down more so for example my
daughter's name
McKinley Fisher is just a little bit
longer than mine she's got a shrink her
as more I've played with hers as well
and hers works pretty well at 0.5 0.5 so
think about your name think about if
it's longer than Dave Fisher if it's
roughly the length of McKinley Fisher
you'll meet about that if it shows the
name Fisher maybe you can make it a
little bigger don't go to much bigger
than my point seven or else it's gonna
go badly but that's a good skirt I'm
just going to leave it in as McKinley
Fisher I kind of like kind of like
seeing her name on there alright so the
next thing I want to do is I want to put
a rectangle below it right so I kind of
want to put like a backing plane so that
it kind of looks looks good so what I'm
gonna do for this backing plane is I'm
gonna make it related to this block down
here so this block down here is 120 wide
and 20 tall so the name plate has to be
a little bit less than 120 and a little
bit less in the height than 20 I'm going
to come down to pixels on all sides so
I'm gonna go with 118 and
maybe it's easier for me to just do than
to describe verbally so I'm gonna make a
block this is gonna be a gold nameplate
just for giggles I'm going to use like a
brighter Google and this nameplate needs
to have a height than a whip to it and
its width is gonna be 1:18 it's that way
it's two pixels less one on each side
than the piece of wood and then it's
length is gonna be 18 and then it's
height is gonna be 1 so those numbers
seem kind of crazy but what they do is
they give you a block that's kind of
like a nameplate that's roughly the
right size so when you put this
nameplate on now you'll know if your
name fits or not so looks like McKinley
Fisher it's pretty good but obviously if
your name doesn't fit now it's the time
to fix that scale so let's take a look
what we got here so if I rotate this
around I can see like a zoom like crazy
zoom in right I can see the one I've got
here is I've got a name which is too
tall and then I've got a name block
that's one call and so there's a little
bit sticking out on this side and a
little bit sticking out on that side I
don't really want a little bit sticking
out on each side so I'm gonna move that
name block down just a little bit so I'm
gonna move it down exactly one
millimeter so my Z is gonna be negative
one and so now it's good to be more
steps so now it creates the name it
shrinks it down I creates the the block
here and then here is the move down
right so it moves it down one pixel and
so now that lettering is all perfectly
on the top right cool
so it's going pretty good so at this
point I've got a name block now what I
want to do is I want to kind of like
rotate it up and move up forwards to the
front of the trophy since I want them to
move together the name and the back.you
piece I need to group them so I'm gonna
create group I can see the Kinley
struggling over here cuz there's
computers I'll help you out this so once
I group on
it's all one good that I need to rotate
them to kind of like flip them up I'm
gonna rotate them about this red line
here which is the x axis by 90 degrees
so I'm gonna see what that looks like
I'm gonna keep using my single step
approach even though it's getting kind
of long it's like I had to click a whole
bunch to go through create group there's
the rotate so now it is rotated up so
it's actually like almost ready to go
the only thing that's wrong is I need to
move it up some and forward some because
right now it's in the middle of the
trophy so this should hopefully be the
last thing I need to do I need to move
it forwards in the Y so the Y is this
green line here so if I want to move it
forwards on the Y that's actually the
negative Y direction and I'm going to
move it negative 16 the reason for the
negative 16 is because that wooden block
was 30 1/2 of 30 is 15 and then it has a
little bit of thickness as well so I
needed to bump it out to negative 16 I
also need to move it up in the Z
direction because you can see it's kind
of like partly below ground and I need
to move it up 10 so that it's in the
middle of that block so now I can do
eyes I can run my whole thing right so
it makes my name it makes the plate for
it it rotates it up it moves it into
position and then it starts creating the
the rest of the trophy
it's going pretty good and then the
block is over awesome now for your
animation if you want your animation to
happen in a different order you totally
can you can do it in any order you would
like to be perfectly honest so if you
want this to happen later you can just
very carefully move it later in the code
you can move it to the middle if you
wanted to right doesn't doesn't really
matter but if I run it now you can see
those the top thing first and then after
the top thing is done then it's going to
do my name plate second just showing
that you can do whatever order you want
and then it's going to do the
blacks and the blocks third pretty cool
would this have been easier to do with
the 3d modelers and blocks I don't know
it's really just kind of an opportunity
to learn how to use coding to do 3d
models from here what you can do is you
can export it if you have a 3d printer
you could get an STL file and you could
print it or if you wanted you could
export it as a part and then you could
just save the part to where you can edit
it somewhere else right
McKinley truth let me save that part now
I could also share it so I could make an
animated gif of it or screenshots those
are some things you could do if you did
choose to save it as a part what you
could do is you could now you can open
it in the regular 3d modeler if you
wanted to go that route so I'm going to
go ahead and show that step just just
for fun so in 3d designs I say create
new part and what I'm gonna do is I now
have that part in my library so it's
called my perk collection right so here
is McKinley's trophy that I made in
blocks we couldn't drag it over I drop
it right there cool and then once it's
in here you can do more things in here
if you wanted so you can kind of go back
and forth between these things and then
from over here you could actually like
get it 3d printed through one of these
one of these communities I haven't ever
done one of these because I don't need
to I've got access to a 3d printer but
no no the decatur right alright so I
finished the the rest of that kind of
quick McKinley I know you fell behind a
little bit you want to show the work
that you got so far
finish already finished you were able to
keep up with that that touring pace of
zing
so we'll see the the speed of the
Kinley's computer here so she's got it
set to max a little speed this is what
happens when your dad gives you a 10
year old computer right looking great
you got the bass on there and then right
now it's doing the McKinley Fisher stuff
and then it's going to pop right to the
front here just a second isn't it three
two one boom go I didn't like codeblocks
did you text based programming yeah
thanks mate for really is hard you enjoy
your code camp this week yeah thank you
so much for joining us thank you as well
for joining us today is been great
having you hopefully you've enjoyed the
camp
we'll see you some other time all right
[Music]